[{"answer": "Well, I didn't see it that way at all.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "How do you see it?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, if in fact his history is relevant, if the state makes it such that it's relevant, we have to look at the fact that he was on pot and we know that he had at least enough in his system that the state experts suggest that there could have been impairment.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "What is the material relevance really to what happened as you say in the crucial six, seven minutes?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, that's why I asked for an anonymous jury.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "How are you viewing that process?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "There is somebody I think it was on your program, Piers, who said a long time ago that no matter how this case ends up, it's not going to end well for America.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think, Mark O'Mara, that we're ever going to really know what happened, and if we don't know the answer to that question, is it likely to be a tinderbox whatever verdict comes in?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I'll say Attorney O'Mara is not being intellectually honest if he doesn't denote the racial undertones in this case.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "What is your reaction to George Zimmerman's attorney's comments?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think Attorney O'Mara and the defense team helped the matter by releasing all those photographs and these text messages that they knew were going to be inadmissible.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "What is your view of how this process should play out?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Well, very briefly, a year ago I had a conversation with Ben Crump and I told him that he needed to be very careful putting Trayvon Martin on such a high pedestal because he's really just a 17-year-old that comes to the table with whatever he came with, and now a year later they suggest that what we did to put out the evidence that the family and Mr. Crump was aware of for the whole past year, they knew who their son is, they know who he was, they knew about the suspensions, they knew about the charges, they knew about all that.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "And you want something to say?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Monster tornado, I'd say at least a half mile wide and the city of Salina definitely dodged a bullet.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Reed, what can you tell me?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Well, I think we have to keep the evidence relevant to the law of self-defense.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "What do you make of the argument so far?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Well, it wouldn't be very relevant evidence.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Right, but Alan, I mean, call me naive here, but how many times has marijuana been used as evidence that somebody's been murderously violent?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "What did you make of what happened last Thursday?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Because the state proved their case.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Alan, is there an argument that this should be unanimous or nothing in these things?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well, it's something horrible, definitely.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "How are you feeling about the fact your mother tonight is in a Mexican jail and facing very serious charges?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Yes, I saw her -- I went to visit her on Saturday, and that was one of the hardest things I think I've ever had to do.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Have you been able to speak to her?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "I mean, has your mother, Anna, ever been involved in any way with drugs in her life?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I believe -- I mean, I've heard things that Senator Flake is helping and some other people are involved, which makes me feel good about, you know, being a citizen and the place we live and my mom being a citizen as well.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Is there anyone trying to help you?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "You know, all I can say is there was a misunderstanding.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "What is your belief, Anna, about what has happened here?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Do you think she's been set up?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "You know, I come from a strong family from my mother.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "ORGAN: How is the family all coping without her, knowing where she is?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I'm doing well.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Ben, how are you?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Hey, don't mess with the big guys.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Who would have put money on Chris Christie beating President Obama at any form of sport?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "You know what, I asked that today.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Why do we care about Chris Christie's weight?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "You've always got to ask yourself what could you accomplish even if you were to do a lot.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "It's an interesting book, very timely obviously, particularly with a lot of people looking at John McCain, who was in Syria today, looking at what's happening in Syria and saying, post-Iraq, Afghanistan, the different tone that President Obama took in Libya, what is the right thing to do now in these tinderbox countries when they kick off?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "In principle, they should be.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Should they be taking more of the global policeman responsibility, letting America perhaps focus on what it needs to do, as many argue, back here on domestic turf?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I think on balance, these interventions have probably set back terrorism.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Where do you sit?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Well, we ought to obviously push back.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "What should America be doing about that?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I think the clearest success over the last 50 or 25 years was the First Iraq War, the Gulf War, where the United States went in with great international support, with limited goals, clearly --", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Or has it all just been a bit of a mess, but a mess that had to happen?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Absolutely, to restore Kuwaiti sovereignty, to get the Iraqis out, to cut the Iraqis down to size.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "With a clear objective?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Actually I think that it sort of think it furthers the spelling bee.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "What difference will that make, do you think?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Now, do you know what that word means?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "OK, antidisestablishmentatrianism: A-N-T-I-D-I-S-E-S-T-A- B-L-I-S-H-M-E-N-T-A-R-I-A-N-I-S-M", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "I think that is probably right, but I'm going to ask Snigdha is she right?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Go on, have a guess.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "I could take a guess?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Well, I guess if you break it down, it's anti- disestablishment.", "docId": "130528pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Snigdha, do you know?", "qSentId": 560}]